# Ghulam Zakariya

## Flutter Developer

khanzakariya22@gmail.com +923042207456 Lahore, Pakistan

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ghulamzakariya-flutterdeveloper 🙍 Zakariya#6519

S https://join.skype.com/invite/UjkQBGetoIm7 fver. gzack22

## PROFILE

Mobile Programer with 3-year experience in mobile development(Android native&Flutter) Looking for opportunities as a software developer with an expert team of developers who will help advance my career progression to senior positions in the future.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

03/2021 - 12/2021 Mait

Lahore Flutter Developer

01/2022 - 11/2022 My Technology (pvt) Lahore Flutter Developer

12/2022 - present Simplex TS Technology solutions

Lahore, Pakistan Senior Flutter Developer

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Bs Software Engineering**

Comsats University

#### **Intermediate**

BISE, DG Khan

		SKI	LLS
--	--	-----	-----

• java

• oop

• Clean Code

• Git

Getx

• Provider

• Firebase

• Google Maps

• sqllite

• Bloc

• Team Work

• Stripe

• Analystical thinking

• Problem Solving

• Dart

localization

• Postman

• Agile

• xcode

## LANGUAGES

English Urdu Sariki



• Gaming • travelling • Circket

Hockey

#### PROJECTS

05/2024 - 08/2024 **DsofU** 

Employee App

Its employee app for Dubai South Employees where they can do everything like submit leave , expense claim, create memo, generate payslips and apply for documnets and many more

05/2023 – present

KFC Pakistan

Burger app where you can order burger at home also pick and enjoy

**Play Store** = https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=io.bramerz.kfc&hl=en&gl=US

**App Store** = https://apps.apple.com/us/app/kfc-pakistan/id1480491422

12/2022 - 05/2023

Domino's Pizza Pakistan

Implementation the functioning of pizza app where you can order your pizza through this app . You can also do future order in this app . And get your pizza at home

**Play Store** = https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=pk.com.dominos&hl=en&gl=US

**App Store** = https://apps.apple.com/pk/app/dominos-pakistan/id1453983132

10/2022 - 12/2022

Term me

Implements the functioning of an E-commerce App that performs various functions like sign up, logout, add to cart, billing, and much more.

07/2022 - 10/2022

Cabane

Implements the functioning of an E-commerce App that performs various functions like sign up, logout, add to cart, billing, and much more,

04/2022 - 07/2022

**Build It** 

Implements the functioning of an E-commerce App that performs various functions like sign up, logout, add to cart, billing, and much more,

01/2022 - 04/2022

Play Papa

Implements the functioning of an E-commerce App that performs various functions like sign up, logout, add to cart, billing, and much more,

Play Store =

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=net.playpapa.mytech

App Store = https://apps.apple.com/pk/app/play-papa/id6443879106

09/2021 - 12/2021

Hukum Janab

Implements the functioning of an E-commerce App that performs various functions like sign up, logout, add to cart, billing, and much more,and also provide servies to your to hire workers to do your work

Google Play Store: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.hukumjanab

04/2021 - 07/2021

Book bus

This App is for book tickets for your route online and pay from stripe